Take it easy, Peter.
放松点,Peter
Not the kind of research you expected, huh?
不是你预期的那种研究吧,啊?
Relax.
放松点
Sit back and enjoy the ride.
坐好了慢慢在后面兜风吧
Take a shot in his head!
射它的头
Lord, have mercy.
哦,上帝!
My arm!
我的胳膊!
So, what do you think?
嗯,你现在感觉如何?
Glad you came, right?
很高兴你加入,不是吗?
You said you wanted to be rich.
你曾说过想做个有钱人的
Well, this is what it looks like.
呵呵,想做有钱人就要象这个样子
Glad you made yourself comfortable.
很高兴你能好好待着
God!
我的天!
God help us.
上帝帮帮我们吧.
《狂蟒之灾3：魂泣山溪》
So, what you're stating is that Wexel Hall Pharmaceuticals...
那么,你说的是 Wexel Hall制药公司...
...have denied knowledge of genetic testing...
...否认动物基因测试...
...on animals at their secret labs in Eastern Europe.
...在他们东欧的秘密实验室
The fact that CEO J.D. Murdoch personally contacted Peter...
事实上CEO J.D. Murdoch先生亲自联系了Peter...
...to deny these claims, we feel gave total credence...
...意图否认这些传言,我们觉得这就更加证明了...
...to the leak that testing was more inhumane than we have ever seen.
...泄露的测试内容是罕见的残忍
Can you be more specific without divulging your informants?
在不泄露你内线的前提下,你可以再详细一些吗?
Our sources reported and I quote:
我引用及我们的报告:
"The testing we witnessed is more cruel, more grotesquely evil...
"我们所见的试验残忍,邪恶的程度...
...than the American people could ever imagine. "
...完完全全超出美国人所能的想象"
Good morning, Mr. Murdoch.
早安,Murdoch先生.
Stay.
待在这里
Good morning, Mr. Murdoch.
早安,Murdoch先生.
Handshake says a lot about a man, Pinkus.
握手很能说明一个人, Pinkus.
Yes, sir.
是的,先生.
Can I get you a cup of coffee, sir?
来杯咖啡吗,先生?
Cut the pleasantries.
废话少说.
There's been a leak.
消息泄露了
A leak?
泄露了?
PETA.
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals...
善待动物组织的人
...have launched an inquiry with public relations.
...向公众发起了调查
Where exactly is our facility and what exactly are we doing there?
我们的设备在哪及我们到底在做什么?
Now I'm asking myself, "How did they find out about us?"
现在我也扪心自问, "他们是如何发现我们的?"
Well, I can assure you, Mr. Murdoch. I will find out.
我向你保证, Murdoch先生.我会找出原因的
I am the public face of Wexel Hall.
我是Wexel Hall公司的脸皮.
When that face is damaged...
当脸皮被毁的时候...
- I am damaged. - I understand, sir.
- 我也同时被毁. - 我明白,先生.
Not to mention that every drug company in the world...
更不用说世界上的每个制药公司...
...is crawling up our ass, trying to beat us to the finish line.
...都想要尽一切办法置我们于死地.
I could double security but until we've identified the source...
我们可以加强安保但如果找不出消息泄露源的话...
- it would be pointless. - It is your job!
- 那一切都白瞎. - 这是你的活!
And you will do your job.
并且你必须把它做好.
Or the only thing you'll be supervising is a proctologist...
否则你就只能给我去肛肠研究部门...
...removing my boot from your rectum. Do you understand?
...去研究如何把我的鞋从你的肠子里取出来,明白吗?
Yes, sir.
是的,先生
What is the status of the project?
项目的进度如何?
We've hit some delays.
有些延迟了
You've hit some delays. Now why is it I'm not surprised?
延迟! 我现在可真一点都不吃惊了
What sort of delays?
哪方面延迟了?
Kane will answer all your questions.
Kane将回答你所有的问题
Where is Kane?
Kane在哪里?
Just this way, sir.
这边走,先生
This is a live feed of the queen anaconda's tank.
这是活体蟒后养殖间
Completely motionless.
根本不动啊
Just like my first wife.
就像我的第一任老婆
Don't let her slumber fool you.
别被她的小憩欺骗了你
She's 1200 pounds of pure crushing power.
她可是有1200磅的粉碎式力量
As I said, just like my first wife.
正如我说的,就像我的第一任老婆
Good to see you, Mr. Murdoch.
很高兴见到你,Murdoch先生.
I wasn't expecting you until next week.
我以为你下星期才来的
Professor, as you know, I'm a man in a hurry.
教授,如你所知,我可是个急性子
Our staff's been working around the clock...
我们的人员一直努力工作...
...and I'm fully aware of your schedule.
...我也注意了你的时间安排
Good. Because I'm paying you for results.
很好. 因为为成果付钱的是我
As you know, we have successfully synthesized and produced...
如你所知,我们已经成功的合成和生产...
...a blood-orchid extract.
...血兰提取物.
Our patient tolerates the serum just like snakes in the wild do...
我们患者对血清的适应力和那些野生蛇一样...
...with zero negative side effects.
...完全没有副作用
And no signs of aging.
没有发现衰变.
The synthetic serum is fully efficacious.
这个合成的血清肯定是有效的
Yes, at present only in snakes.
是的,目前只是对蛇来说
But there is something you must see.
但这里有些东西你必须看看...
Please?
请
This is more like it.
这才有点意思.
But tell me, what is it that snakes have that we don't have?
但是告诉我,我们比蛇少了什么?
We still have not determined why the extract is non-toxic in the snake...
我们目前还无法解释为什么这种提取物对蛇是无害的...
...but lethal in humans.
...但对人却是致命的
But you told me you had made some progress.
但你告诉我你已经有进展
There has been. We've reduced but not eliminated the toxicity.
是的,我们只是减少,但没有完全去除毒性
- In dogs and in chimpanzees. - Even mice.
- 狗和黑猩猩都做了试验 - 还有老鼠.
Mice administered a steady dose of the serum...
给老鼠连续注射一定剂量的这种血清...
...show signs of a reduced rate of aging.
...衰变的速率降低了
But ultimately, they die...
但最后,它们还是死了...
...from some mechanism we don't fully understand.
...因为某些我们也搞不明白的机理吧.
Mr. Murdoch, this is Darryl.
Murdoch先生, 这是Darryl.
Hello, Darryl.
你好, Darryl.
Nice to meet you, sir.
很高兴见到您,先生
- This way, sir. - Impressive.
- 这边,先生 - 不错
Very impressive.
非常不错
Well, the bottom line, Mr. Murdoch...
嗯,现在情况是,Murdoch先生...
...is that we've developed a second-generation serum...
...通过培育新一代的兰花...
...by producing a new strain of the orchid.
...我们制造了第二代血清
We hope to solve the problem at the source.
我们希望能在源头解决这个问题
Behold the miracle of modern science.
看看现代科学的奇迹
Behold the miracle? I can't see anything.
看看奇迹?我可什么都没有看见
We keep it dark to create an artificial sleep cycle for the creature.
我们通过保持黑暗以给这个东西一种睡眠的感觉
Ugly son of a bitch, isn't it?
真他妈的够丑的吧?
What is that?
那是什么?
It was a typical anaconda.
典型的水蚺
It certainly isn't typical now.
当然现在它不典型了.
- How's my baby doing today? - He's hungry again.
- 我宝宝今天如何? - 又饿了.
- What's the ambient temp of the cage? - Sixty-five.
- 笼子里温度多少? - 65.
Let's cozy it up five degrees.
提高5度.
And increase the cynanol mix by 20 cc's.
同时加20立方厘米的混合气体.
Okay.
OK.
Are you telling me a regular dosage of serum is what's produced this?
你是在告诉我这是由常规剂量的血清产生的?
For the most part, we wanted to see...
很大程度上, 我们最想看的...
Amazing. Four months ago, he could fit in a shoebox.
太神奇了,四月前他还可以被装进一个鞋盒呢
That's probably how he feels right now.
他现在可能也还这么觉得
Suits are here.
制服在这里
Yeah, I know. And I intend to find out why.
嗯,我知道了,我要去找出原因来
In fact, quite the opposite.
事实上,正好相反
It's bigger, faster, stronger.
它变的更大,更快,更强
And a hell of a lot meaner.
还更加卑劣
We're making progress but we need larger tanks and additional security.
我们正取得进展, 不过我们需要更大的实验室和更好的安保
- I was getting to that. - Were you?
- 我正要说这个问题 - 是吗?
Mr. Murdoch, our herpetologist, Dr. Amanda Hayes.
Murdoch先生, 我们的爬虫专家Amanda Hayes博士.
I've submitted four requests to Pinkus.
我向Pinkus提了四个申请.
And every time his answer is, "It's not my call."
每次他总是回答 "这不是我说了算的"
So whose call is it?
那么到底谁说了算?
Yours, Mr. Murdoch?
您, Murdoch先生?
Please excuse Dr. Hayes.
请原谅Hayes博士.
She's not familiar with the protocol.
她不清楚协议
I'm very familiar with the protocol.
我很清楚协议.
I'm doing what you pay me for.
我做你付钱要我做的事
Minding the well-being of our reptiles and watching our asses.
在乎一下我们动物的情况和我们自己的安全
Dr. Hayes.
Hayes博士.
You give me a marketable product...
你能给我有市场前景的产品...
...and I will buy you the biggest animal park this side of the equator.
...那么我就会给你买下这个半球最大的动物园.
We need larger facilities now.
我们现在需要更大的设备
I'll see what I can do.
我看看我能做什么
You have to do better than that. You're not handling 60-foot snakes...
你必须给我大一些的设备 Y你可没有对付过一条60尺...
...with massive appetites.
...并且胃口很大的蟒蛇.
We are understaffed and in way over our heads.
我们根本就没有足够的人手
What does she mean by that?
她说的那个是什么意思?
If you'll excuse me, gentlemen, I have some cultures to examine.
不好意思,先生,我还有一些菌要培养
Pinkus.
- It's nothing. - Nothing?
- 这没什么的. - 没什么?
I'm paying you an obscene amount of money to keep this research on track.
我付给你们这么多钱,就是要让研究照计划运行
It is clearly not on track.
很显然现在并非如此.
And my very expensive expert there is concerned.
还要让我再多花一笔不菲的钱去搞定这个专家所说的事情
Money is not the problem.
钱不是问题
If we stopped every time we needed to expand or upgrade...
假如我们停下来更新和扩大...
...we'd be months behind.
...我们就要推后几个月.
Everything here is custom-made. It takes time.
这的一切都是定制好的. 需要时间.
And time is what I do not have.
我少的就是时间.
- Amanda? Excuse us. - Sir? Sure.
- Amanda?借一步说话. - 先生?可以
What is the matter with you?
你到底是怎么回事?
I didn't go to med school to serve a life sentence.
我上医学院可不是服无期徒刑
It's just a means to an end.
不过是为了达到目地的一种方式
Whose end? For what?
谁的目地?为什么
So some sick billionaire can defeat death?
为了一些生病的亿万富翁能战胜死亡?
- What do you mean he's sick? - Come on, Eric.
- 你说他有病是什么意思? - 得了, Eric.
You didn't see it?
你难道看不出来?
Pupils dilated, pale skin, coughing?
瞳孔放大,皮肤惨白,不停咳嗽?
Not to mention his severe weight loss?
更别提他体重的急剧下降
It looks to me like he's got cancer, which means he's dying.
我看他得了癌症,也就是说快咯屁了
Amanda.
We're at the brink of saving millions of lives.
我们正在拯救千万人的生命
Can you imagine a drug that could revitalize cancer patients...
你能想象一种药让癌症患者获得新生...
...and reverse Alzheimer's?
...还有能逆转老年痴呆症?
Do you really still believe that?
你真的还相信那个?
Don't you?
你不相信吗?
I don't know.
我不知道
For something that's supposed to be so good, why does it feel wrong?
这本应该蛮好的,为什么就是觉得有什么不对头呢?
You knew what we were doing when we started the research.
你从试验开始的时候就知道我们在做什么
Yeah, but I expected it to be handled with more responsibility.
是的,不过我觉得应该更负责的去做这些
We're tampering with evolution, Eric.
我们被一些进展所迷惑了, Eric.
Come on. It's just a big snake.
得了,不就是一条大蛇嘛.
Yeah, well, that's definitely an understatement.
是的,对,说得蛮轻巧的
- All right, I'll talk to you later, okay? - Okay.
- 好吧,等下和你说,可以吗? - 可以.
Bigger, tougher, meaner, eh?
更大,更强,更卑劣,哦?
I could use a bit of that.
我能用上那个
That's not a good idea, sir.
那不是个好注意,先生.
You're telling me the serum is responsible for this?
你告诉我是血清导致了这个?
Sir? Sir, turn that light off.
先生? 先生, 把灯关掉.
Turn that light off.
关掉灯.
What the hell happened there?
那鬼地方到底怎么了?
Pinkus? The warning lights in the tank are starting to go crazy.
Pinkus? 试验间里的警灯狂闪不停了.
- What's going on? - I told you not to do that.
- 怎么了? - 我告诉你别那么做的.
- Hit the gas. - What's going on?
- 放毒气. - 怎么了?
- What's going on? - More lights are flashing.
- 怎么了? - 更多的灯开始闪了.
There's a lot of movement.
动作很大
- Don't you touch that gas! - Darryl, hit the goddamn gas!
- 别放毒气! - Darryl, 马上放毒气!
- You're gonna kill it. - No, we're not killing...
- 你会杀了它的. - 不,我们不会...
- Don't put the gas on. - Please, Darryl!
- 别放毒气. - 求你了, Darryl!
- Hit the goddamn gas. Sir. Sir. - I won't let you kill it!
- 放毒气,先生,先生! - 我不会让你杀了它的!
Calm down. It will only sedate the snake.
冷静. 这仅仅是让蛇安静下来的.
Don't you tell me what...
别跟我说...
- Darryl! Darryl? - What's happening?
- Darryl! Darryl? - 怎么回事?
- What's happening? - Darryl...
- 发生什么事了? - Darryl...
Look, look. Don't worry, Mr. Murdoch. That's three-inch polycarbonate glass.
看,看,别当心Murdoch先生. 那是3寸厚的有机玻璃
Well, it's not enough.
哦,我觉得还不够
- What's it doing? - Everybody, just stay calm.
-它在做什么? - 大家保持镇定
- The gas will sedate it. - Are you sure?
- 毒气会使它安静的. - 你确定?
He'll settle down, I'm sure.
他会安静的,我确定
Everybody calm down.
大家镇定点
It's fine.
现在好了
Finally.
结束了
Now let's just leave him be.
现在就让他一个蟒待着吧
Darryl, call Kane.
Darryl, 告诉Kane
Let him know what happened.
让他知道发生的一切
I'll call the technicians to get this repaired.
我去叫技术人员来修理这东西
- Darryl. Hit the alarm. Lock us down. - Hit the alarm! Hit the alarm!
- Darryl. 快按警报器,把我们隔离开 - 快按,快啊!
Loading results...
下载结果中...
Everyone outside.
所有人都离开.
Stay calm. Everyone outside. Let's go.
保持镇定,所有人马上离开 马上离开
- We're safe. - We gotta help him.
- 我们安全了 - 我们快救救他吧
- What? Screw him. - He's my friend.
- 什么? 别管他了 - 他是我朋友
- There's a monster out there! - I've got to help him!
- 那边可有只大怪兽啊! - 我不管,我得去救他!
If the snake doesn't get you, the gas will!
就算那蛇不杀了你,那毒气也会毒死你的
Now, shut up!
你他妈给我闭嘴!
Oh, my God.
哦,我的上帝
- What happened? - What do you think?
- 发生什么了? - 你以为呢?
What the hell did you do? Where's Darryl?
你都做了什么刚才? Darryl哪儿去了?
Darryl didn't make it.
Darryl没有逃出来
We've gotta go. Let's go.
我们快走,马上
- You said the gas would knock it out. - He's looking for a way out.
- 你刚才不是说毒气可以搞定它吗. - 他在找出口.
We have to contain him. Security, lockdown.
我们必须控制他,安全小组,关闭通道
- Full lockdown. - Yes, sir.
- 全都关闭. - 是的,先生
I'm locking down right now.
我马上关闭
Amanda, get the guns.
Amanda, 拿上枪.
Hey, hey, hey. Where do you think you're going?
嘿,嘿,嘿,你要去哪里?
- I'm getting Murdoch out of here. - Nobody's going anywhere.
- 我要带Murdoch离开这里 - 没有人可以离开.
Grab a gun!
他妈的赶紧拿把枪去!
- No way. I'm getting out of here. - Pinkus.
- 搞什么,我要马上离开 - Pinkus.
Take the gun!
拿起枪!
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
All personnel should exit immediately to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上离开 去安全的区域
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
- The sedatives must have taken effect. - Are you sure?
- 镇定剂的药效发作了. - 你确定吗?
Yeah. That stuff would knock out 10 rhinos.
是的. 那些剂量足可以放倒10头犀牛.
It's a stun gas. It will only last for five minutes.
那只是镇定气,它只能让他昏迷5分钟
We don't have time. Get the masks.
没时间了,大家快带上面罩
Pinkus? Escort Mr. Murdoch out of here.
Pinkus? 快带Murdoch 先生离开这里
Yeah. Yeah. Sir?
好的,好的,先生?
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
All personnel should exit immediately to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上离开,到安全的区域去.
- Get out. - This is not a drill.
- 快走. - T这不是演习
All personnel should exit immediately to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上撤离到安去的区域去
- Have you seen Janet? Is she outside? - She's already gone.
- 你有看见Janet吗? 她出来了吗? - 她已经走了.
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
All personnel should exit immediately to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上撤离到指定的安全区域
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
All personnel should exit immediately to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上撤离到指定的安全区域
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
All personnel should exit immediately to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上撤离到指定的安全区域
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
All personnel...
所有人...
This is not a drill.
这不是演习
All personnel should exit immediately to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上撤离到指定的安全区域
Okay.
好的
Oh, God.
哦,上帝
- It's Darryl. - All personnel should exit...
- 这是Darryl. - 所有人马上...
...to your designated safety zone.
...到指定的安全区域
- Are you okay? - Come on.
- 你还好吗? - 快.
- Let's get through this. - This is not a drill.
- 让我们度过这关. - 这不是演习
All personnel should exit to your designated safety zone.
所有人马上撤离到指定的安全区域
Where is it?
它在哪?
Over here?
在附近?
This is not a drill.
这不是演习.
- All personnel should exit... - Where is it?
- 所有人马上撤离... - 它在哪?
...to your designated safety zone.
..到指定的安全区域
Oh, God.
哦,上帝
He's not in here.
他不在这里
- Where would he go? - I don't know.
- 他会去哪里? - 我不知道
But we better find it fast.
我们最好快点找到他
He's gone after the queen.
他肯定去找蟒后了
- Let's go. - Come on.
- 走 - 快
This is not a drill. All personnel...
这不是演习,所有人马上离...
How are we gonna explain that one, huh, Pinkus?
那个我们怎么解释,啊,Pinkus?
Don't tell me you haven't got a backup lighting system.
别告诉我你们连后备照明系统都没有
Please don't tell me.
请不要告诉我
It should come on in a minute.
马上就会恢复的
Let's get out of here quickly. Quickly.
我们赶紧离开这里 赶紧
Oh, God.
哦,上帝
I hate when you're right.
我真希望你没有在这里
So do I.
我也是
Susan.
Oh, no. She's gone.
哦,不,她死了
He broke her out.
他救了她出去
This is all my fault.
这全是我的错
Run!
快跑!
Have you any idea what this is gonna cost to cover?
你知不知道我们要花多少代价来隐瞒这些
Yes. No.
是的...不
I mean, yes. I know exactly...
我想说...是的,我知道...
I want this place cleaned!
我要把这里清理干净!
I want it cleaned properly.
别留下任何痕迹
Sir? Might I advise that we can still salvage this situation?
先生,我觉得我们可以挽回
On-site security team is here.
我们有安全小组在现场这里
We have a team of professional trackers on their way.
一队追踪专家也正赶来
You'll do whatever you have to do.
做你所有该做的事
But you will be with them 24 hours a day.
但是你要一天24小时和他们在一起
- What do you mean, sir? - You're a supervisor, Pinkus.
- 什么意思? - 你是监理, Pinkus.
Supervise.
监督好
Otherwise, I will have them test that serum on you.
否则,我也让你成为这血清的试验品
But, sir, I don't do field work.
但是,先生,我不作现场工作
I want news, Pinkus.
Pinkus随时告诉我情况.
- Good news. - Pinkus.
- 好的情况. - Pinkus.
Name's Grozny.
我是Grozny.
Until I hear good news, you will report to me hourly.
你每小时向我汇报直到我听到好消息
Yes, sir.
是,先生
Grozny.
Follow me.
跟我来.
I'll brief you on the situation.
我向你简要说一下情况
Come on, guys. It took five shots to bring them down.
得了,哥们,开了五枪才搞定他们
We'll give you 20 at market rate.
我会给你20%的市场价
Look, guys. I don't care what kinky plans you're into.
听着,哥们,我才不吊你们有什么牛逼的计划
But these are 5-pound Java rhino horns.
但这是五磅重的爪哇犀牛角
So I suggest you go to an ATM teller.
所以我建议你去找个ATM取款机
One that dispenses some respect.
做些有意思的事情
Thirty thousand or nothing.
三万,否则没门
Deal.
成交
Always a pleasure.
乐意效劳
Pleasure.
合作愉快
Give us the envelope.
把信给我
Okay. I got $30,000 in crisp American bills.
好吧,我刚刚拿的可是三万美金
Now, if you want euros you'll have to go to Greece or a bank.
假如你们需要欧元的话,得去希腊或者银行兑换了
I get them confused.
我也常搞混
I'm... Hang on.
我... 有电话
Yeah? Pinkus?
喂? Pinkus?
I'm a little busy right now.
我现在有点忙
What?
什么?
Oh, let me guess.
让我猜猜看
You didn't reinforce the cages and the snakes got out.
你肯定没有把笼子加固好,那蟒蛇逃跑了吧
This is serious.
情况严重了
We are prepared to pay and I need you here to lead the team.
我们会给你开个好价,希望你回来领导这个队伍
Yeah. I'll be there as soon as I can.
好的,我尽快
What? What?
什么?什么?
- What's your name? - Florin.
- 你叫什么? - Florin.
Florin?
- It's for you. - What?
- 你的电话. - What?
Always know the animal before the hunt.
打猎前要先了解猎物
These creatures are one of a kind.
他们是独一无二的
- Growing to become 60 feet long. - Sixty-foot snakes?
- 长到了有60尺长 - 60尺的蛇?
- I've got one of those. - Dreamer.
- 我也有一条大家伙 - 想都别想
Please!
请安静!
They are fast and very strong.
他们又快又强
Having never dealt with anything like this, I urge you to use extreme caution.
我们以前从没有接触过这样的生物, 请你们务必提高警觉
We must bring them down.
我们必须搞定他们
It is imperative.
必须
- And they are more than 60 feet... - Thank you, Dr. Hayes.
- 他们远长于60尺... - 谢谢, Hayes博士.
I will handle this briefing.
我会处理好的
My team know these woods like our own backyard.
我的战队了解这个森林就像了解他们自家的后院一样
It's easier than that. We also know their location.
可能更简单,我们甚至知道他们的藏身处
We try and keep a short leash on our investments.
我们总是实时记录我们的研究成果
In case of emergencies.
以防万一
We're moving out in 10.
10分钟后出发
Hammett's on his way. We should wait.
Hammett's在路上了 我们应该等他
We're not waiting. Not when we know where the snakes are.
我们不能等,尤其是我们已经知道蛇躲在哪里
We need to strike fast.
我们要速战速绝
Like I said, we move out in 10.
如我所说,10分钟后出发.
- Man, he wants all the glory. - You're right.
- 伙计,他想独吞功劳 - 说对了.
You know how he feels about Hammett.
你也知道他怎么看Hammett.
- Yep. - You heard the man.
- 是的 - 你们都听到了.
Ten minutes.
10分钟
I need to speak with you privately.
我需要单独和你谈谈
Why haven't you called the government?
为什么不通知政府?
The company is handling this matter privately.
公司想私下处理好这个事件
Company has no idea what we're dealing with.
公司根本就不明白我们所面对的是什么
Do I need to remind you that you signed a strict confidentiality contract?
我想我不用提醒你,你是签过保密协议的吧
There are innocent people that need to be warned.
开始那些无辜的人需要了解这些情况
Our professionals will resolve this matter swiftly and efficiently.
我们的专家会快速高效得处理好这些事
And as for you, take this as a friendly warning.
对了,我还想给你作为朋友的一个忠告
Do not interfere.
别插手这个事
I am responsible for those animals.
那些动物是我的责任
Nobody knows their behavior better.
每人比我更了解他们的习性
Those snakes aren't gonna bask in the sun and roll over for you.
那些蟒蛇可不会为你在地上打滚
I'm coming with you.
我要和你一起去
You're not the one handling 60-foot snakes with massive appetites.
你是没有应付过一条60尺且胃口超大的蛇
We are understaffed and in way over our heads.
我们根本人手就不够
Can you imagine a drug that could revitalize cancer patients...
你能想象一种药物让癌症患者获得新生...
...and reverse Alzheimer's?
...还可以逆转老年痴呆症?
Do you really believe that?
你真的相信吗?
Don't you?
你不信?
Please excuse Dr. Hayes.
别介意Hayes博士.
She's not familiar with the protocol.
她并不熟悉协议
Miss Hayes?
Hayes小姐?
Yeah?
怎么?
You like traveling light?
你喜欢轻装旅行?
I don't think I'd feel really comfortable with that.
我觉得我带这个不会舒服的
It would make you comfortable...
你会感觉舒服的...
...if you came face to face with a 60-foot snake.
...如果你面对的是一条60尺的大蛇
I already have, remember? I helped create them.
我曾经面对过,记得吗? 我帮忙创造了他们
Besides, that's why you guys are here.
这也是今天你们出现在这里的原因
I'm giving you the best chance to survive.
我只想给你们逃生提供最好的服务
It's no problem, Amanda.
没问题, Amanda.
Just stick with Nick.
只要一直和Nick呆在一起.
Nick?
Introduce her to the bazooka.
把火箭筒介绍给她.
The bazooka.
火箭筒
Twenty-four knockouts, regional city champ.
24场KO, 地区总冠军
Can I see that gun again?
我能再看一下那枪吗?
Oh, sorry.
哦,对不起.
You know, Dragosh...
你知道, Dragosh...
...they say you should never look them in the eyes.
...他们都说永远不要去直视他们.
And? What else?
还有呢?还有什么?
They have the powers of mesmerizing.
他们会催眠
- That's bull. - No, no, no, it's true.
- 胡扯 - 不,不,不,这是真的!
I heard a story of a hunter who stared in the eyes of the anaconda too long.
我听过一个故事说一个猎人盯着一条水蚺太久
Suddenly, he was hypnotized.
突然,他就被催眠了
It swallowed him alive.
它生吞了他
You want me to stuff this rifle down your throat?
你想让我把这把来复枪塞进你的喉咙吗?
Don't be an ass, Andrei. You know he's afraid of snakes.
别乱说了, Andrei. 你知道他怕蛇的
I'm not afraid of snakes. I just don't like them.
我不怕,我只是不喜欢他们罢了
You don't have to like them. You just have to like killing them.
你不用喜欢他们,你只要喜欢去杀他们就可以
I'm fine with that.
很乐意
Damn wolves!
天杀的狼!
We're close.
我们靠近了
- Got it. - Follow them.
- 找到了 - 跟上他们
Well, the signal's coming from around here.
信号就来自这附近
It could be anywhere within 100 yards.
它可能在100码以内的任何地方
These bastards detect heat, so you're always prone to attack.
他们会感知热量,所以你们要随时做好战斗的准备
Don't forget that.
千万别忘了!
Nick? Andrei? See who's home.
Nick? Andrei? 看看谁在屋子里
- Dragosh, check the barn. - All right.
- Dragosh, 检查一下农场. - 好的
- You two, around the back. - Let's go.
- 你两,绕到后面去. - 走.
Come on. Let's go.
来,咱们走
- What about us? - Mr. Pinkus. Miss Hayes.
- 我们呢? - Pinkus先生.Hayes小姐.
Stay put.
就呆在这里
- If they were here, you'd see evidence. - Yeah, you're absolutely right.
- 如果他们来过这里,你会发现一些痕迹的 - 对,你说的完全对
That's why we're looking around.
这就是为什么我们四处找
Grozny.
You may need this.
你可能需要这个
Thanks.
谢了
Hello? Anybody home?
嗨?有人在家吗?
- Hello? - Try the door.
- 哈罗? -试试门.
It's not locked.
没有锁
Why would it be?
怎么会?
It's like Little House on the Prairie.
就像草原上的小屋
Let's check around the back.
我们去检查一下后面
I'm...
我...
...sorry about the professor.
...对教授的死很遗憾.
He was a good man.
他是个好人
Yeah, thanks.
是的,谢谢
Dragosh, it's reading. We're close.
Dragosh, 它显示我们靠近了
Keep your eyes peeled.
睁大你的眼睛
All clear.
检查完毕
Listen, I'm going in. I can't wait anymore.
听着,我要进去,我不想等了
You go around back, I'll take front.
你绕到后面,我走前面
Okay.
好的
Go check over there.
去检查一下那里
Hey, better safe than sorry, huh?
嘿,安全还是比说对不起好点吧?
Be vigilant, guys. We know it's nearby.
警惕点,伙计们 我们知道它就在附近
Come on, guys. It's 60 feet long.
来吧,伙计,它可有60尺呢
The place is deserted, maybe they went out for supplies.
这里没人,可能出去运东西什么的了
That's slightly disturbing.
这可不好玩
What happened to it?
这是怎么回事?
When they don't like a meal they spit it back up.
他们会吐出他们不喜欢的食物
I'd eat it.
我会吃了它
Come on, guys. It's just a goat.
来吧,伙计,只是一只羊
If these beasts only eat things that look good...
假如那些野兽只吃看起来好吃的食物...
...if I were you Miss Hayes, I'd be very careful.
...加入我是你,Hayes小姐, 我会更小心的.
Excuse me?
你说什么?
I hate to interrupt, but we got a job to do.
我无意打断,不过我们还有活要做
Over here.
来这里.
Dragosh, Victor, stay here.
Dragosh, Victor, 呆在这里
Andrei, hang back.
Andrei, 退后.
That makes things a little more difficult.
这让事情有点更难办了
- Tight leash, isn't that what you said? - Let's put Plan B into effect.
- 看好了,这不是你说的吗? - 看来我们要实施B计划了.
And what might that be?
那是什么计划?
I don't know yet.
我还不知道
I don't understand how it sheds so quickly.
我不明白为什么它这么快蜕皮
Ecdysis. It only happens when the snake grows too large for its skin.
蜕皮,只有蛇在长大后皮太小了才会的
Which means it's growing pretty damn fast.
就是说它长得他妈见鬼的快
All right. Victor, I want you to start putting the supplies in order.
好吧. Victor, 我要你把所需物资都准备好
Dragosh, set up a lookout around here.
Dragosh, 在附近站岗
Andrei, around the back.
Andrei, 绕到后面
Nick?
Oh, God! No!
哦,上帝,不
Get him! Go! Go!
抓住他,上,上
Get it!
抓住他
Over there! Outside!
那里,在外面!
Go! Go!
上!上!
Take that, you son of a bitch.
干掉这个狗娘养的东西
Go! Go! Go!
上 上 上!
- Come on. Come on. - Go. Go.
-快!快! - 上 上
- Get something. Check the jeep. - There it is.
- 拿点什么来,去吉普车里找找啊. - 它在那
Quick! Get my bag.
快,拿我的包来.
Get it!
快去拿!
How is he?
他怎么样了?
Dragosh!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
停火!停火!
Amanda, help Grozny.
Amanda, 救救Grozny.
Pinkus, in Grozny's jeep there's a fire extinguisher.
Pinkus,在 Grozny的吉普车里有个灭火器
The rest of you follow me. We end this now.
剩下的跟我来 我们来结束这一切.
Come on.
快.
- Let's go. Come on. - Right.
- 来,快. - 好
Fire extinguisher.
灭火器
Hurry up!
快点!
Stop!
停!
- What? - Sofia. Andrei.
- 什么? - Sofia. Andrei.
Victor.
Hurry up! Hurry up! Come on!
快! 快点! 过来!
- Get my bag! - Where is it?
- 拿我的包来! - 它在哪里?
- Hurry up! - What?
- 快点! - 什么?
- Come on! - Just a sec... I'm coming.
- 快点! - 等... 来了.
Open it up. Quick.
快打开它
- Hurry! - Okay. Hold on.
- 快! - 好的等下.
- I don't know which... - Hold him down.
- 我不知道是哪个... - 按住他.
Give me the elastic.
给我橡皮带
- There. - No, the elastic.
- 给. - 不是,橡皮带.
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道,我不知道
- Give me the elastic. - There, there.
- 给我橡皮带 - 这,给
Now hold him down. Hold him down.
现在按住他,按住他
- Pinch this artery. - I don't know what I'm doing.
- 捏住动脉. - 我不知道要怎么做
Pinch off his artery. Hang in there!
按住他动脉按住那里!
I don't know what I'm doing, Amanda. I don't know.
我不知道我该怎么做, Amanda. 我真不知道.
Just put pressure and don't let go.
就按住就可以,不要放手
- Right here. Don't let go. - Okay.
- 就这,不要放手 - 好好.
- Okay? - It's okay, Grozny.
- 可以吗? - 没事的, Grozny.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty.
这, 小猫咪,小猫咪,小猫咪.
Where are you?
你在哪里?
Where are you hiding, huh?
你藏在哪里了啊?
Come on.
快出来.
- I see it. - Where? Where?
- 我看见它了 - 哪?在哪?
Twelve o'clock.
12点方向
Got it.
看到了
There.
那里
- Damn, it's big. - Let's go!
- 靠.真他妈大 - 上!
Sofia!
Come on.
快出来.
Got something for you.
我有东西给你
That's not good.
那可不太好
- Put pressure! - I don't feel a pulse!
- 压住! - 我感觉不到脉搏了!
- He doesn't have a pulse. It's over! - Shut the hell up!
- 他没有脉搏了,结束了! - 闭上你的鸟嘴!
Amanda, he is gone!
Amanda, 他死了!
- Shut the hell up. Just put... - Amanda, it's over!
- 闭嘴. 就压着... - Amanda, 结束了!
No. Come on. Come on.
不,快醒醒,快醒醒
Amanda, he's dead.
Amanda, 他已经死了.
Come on.
醒醒.
Victor.
Come on.
快点.
Don't move.
别动
You take the cake for leaving without me.
我没来你们就自己开搞了啊!
It wasn't my idea.
这不是我的主意
- We have to kill it. - Take it easy!
- 我们必须杀了它 - 别紧张!
What do you wanna do? Grab it by the tail?
你想做什么? 抓住它的尾巴?
- We're gonna find this thing. Relax. - It's about time, Hammett.
- 我们要先找到那东西,放松. - 是时候了, Hammett.
Good to see you too, Nick. Come on. Gather around.
很高兴再次见到你, Nick. 快,大家集合
- We gotta make a plan. - Hammett.
- 我们制定一个计划. - Hammett.
- Hammett. - Andrei, get the steel case...
- Hammett. - Andrei, 拿出那个铁箱子...
...in the back of my car.
...在我车的后备箱.
All right. Listen up, guys. We've all worked together before.
好了,听着,伙计们.我们以前都合作过的
Simple rules, okay?
简单的规则,明白?
Once you see this thing, you unload everything until it stops moving.
你一旦看到那东西,不要做任何事直到它不动了.
And you shoot only for the head.
然后只冲它的头开火
Nothing else will bring this thing down.
打其他地方都是没有用的
Follow my lead, I'll take you up this snake's ass. Let's go.
跟随我,我就会带领你们把这个蛇干掉! 好了,咱们走
What's that?
那是什么?
It's a tracking device.
追踪装置
Victor, you, Sofie, Amanda in the jeep.
Victor, 你, Sofie, Amanda 上这吉普车里.
Nick, Pinkus, you're with me and Andrei.
Nick, Pinkus,你们和我和 Andrei在一起.
- I think I'll stay here. - Suit yourself.
- 我想我还是呆这里 - 随你便.
But you're gonna miss all the excitement.
但你会错过很多精彩时刻的
We're getting close. The signal is becoming stronger.
我们接近了,信号越来越强了
There!
那!
Come on!
快!
Don't lose it.
别让它跑了.
We're almost there.
我们很接近了
- Stay with them. - I am!
- 跟好他们. - 我在努力!
Come on!
快点!
This way. Quick.
这边,快
We got it. I repeat, we got it. Stay on it!
我们找到了,重复,我们找到了.跟好它
- I am trying. - Try harder.
- 我在努力 - 那就更努力些
Andrei, lose the tracker. We're onto him now.
Andrei, 放下追踪器,我们跟上它了
It's the end of the line for these bastards.
这个狗娘养的死期就要到了
Damn it, try to keep this car steady.
操,把车试着开稳点
- You okay? - Thanks.
-你还好把? - 多谢.
Don't mention it.
别客气
How is that possible?
这怎么可能?
It's burning!
这在灼烧我!
- It just spit on my face. - You okay?
- 它刚刚喷到我的脸. - 你怎么样?
- Cover your eye. Go! - Where is he?
- 捂好你的眼睛,上! - 他在哪里?
Drive, quick.
快开,快.
- Where is he? - Go left. Go.
- 他在哪里? - 左边,走.
It's burning.
这灼烧着我的脸.
I think my leg is broken. My leg.
我想我的腿断了,我的腿.
Victor?
Victor.
Oh, God.
哦,天啊
Sofia?
Sofia.
- Amanda? - Do you see him?
- Amanda? - 你看到他了吗?
Amanda, I think my leg is broken.
Amanda,我想我的腿断了.
Okay. Okay. I'm coming.
好的,好的,我来了
My leg.
我的腿
Amanda.
Amanda. You all right?
Amanda. 你还好吗?
- Amanda. - Hammett.
Hammett.
Oh, my God. No, no, no.
哦,天啊,不 不 不!
Oh, God, just get me out of here. Please.
哦,天啊,帮我离开这里,求你了
No.
不
Hey, hey, hey. It's okay. It's okay.
嘿 嘿 嘿 现在没事了,没事了.
He didn't see me. It must be the mud.
一定是我身上的泥让它看不到我
- He couldn't sense me. - Where are the others?
- 它感觉不到我 - 其他人在哪?
- They're dead. - All right.
-都死了 - 好了没事了.
Let's catch up with Nick and Andrei. You'll be all right.
我们要跟上Nick和Andrei. 你会没事的
What have I done?
我都做了些什么啊?
I don't know what's going on. Murdoch called and said I should be here.
我不知道是怎么回事Murdoch打电话叫我过来
- I have no idea why he didn't call. - Do you think it's possible?
- 我真不明白你为什么不早点打给我?. - 你觉得可能吗?
Is what possible?
什么可能吗?
- Amanda... - What's going on?
- Amanda... - 怎么了?
- Nothing. - Oh, really.
- 没什么 - 哦,真的.
Like you guys are here discussing the weather.
像你们这样的家伙难道会在这里谈论天气吗
You wanna give us a moment.
能给我们几分钟吗
Gladly.
没问题
What?
什么?
We were discussing the possibilities of bringing this creature down.
我们只是在谈论是否可能制服他们
Oh, really? How come I don't believe you?
哦,真的? 我怎么就是不信呢?
You don't even know me.
你根本就不怎么了解我
I've worked with Pinkus enough to know he's always got an agenda.
我和Pinkus一起工作的时间足够长到让我 知道他总有小算盘的
When I see someone I don't trust talking to another I don't trust...
当我看到一个我不相信的人 和另一个我不相信的人谈论的时候...
...I don't get all warm and fuzzy inside.
...我可高兴不起来
That's where the whiskey comes in, darling.
我真不知道要怎么说,亲爱的
You two vipers can talk business all you want. I'm gonna go call the Army.
你们两小丑慢慢聊,我要去通知军方了
Damn, you sure are hot when you're making threats.
该死的,你威胁人的时候很惹火的哦
I'm not making any threats. I'm gonna go call the Army.
我根本没威胁你 我只不过要通知军方罢了
She's hiding something big.
她在隐藏着什么重要的事情
- Yeah, the Army. - What do you mean?
- 是的,军方. - 你什么意思?
I'm not sure but she knows something.
我不确定她到底都知道了些什么
- Your fault. - My fault? I don't think so.
- 你的错 - 我的错?我可不这么想
- I got a bad feeling about her. - Let's find out what it is.
- 我对她没有好感觉 - 咱们去把事情问个明白
I may not have a fancy Ph.D., but I know one thing.
我可能没有见鬼的博士学位, 但我知道一点
There ain't a snake on this planet that can skewer people with its tail.
这个星球上根本没有用尾巴就可以刺穿人的蛇
We weren't expecting this much trouble.
我们没有料到有这么多麻烦
- Really? - What are you two discussing?
- 真的? - 你们在谈论什么?
Yeah, Amanda, why don't you tell them. What were we discussing?
好吧, Amanda,为什么你不告诉他们, 我们在谈论什么
A serum.
一种血清
Okay. We gave it a serum.
好了,我们给它注射了一种血清
Sort of a DNA tune-up.
一种转基因的
Transgenics.
就是转基因
Snakes are the only animals that can tolerate the new serum.
蛇是唯一能适应这种血清的动物
We had to find out why.
我们要找出为什么
So we altered its DNA...
于是我们转化它的DNA...
...in an attempt to isolate the gene that makes it immune to toxicity.
...试图把它免疫毒性的基因分离出来
And the enormous size of the spike in the tail is because of the drugs?
而它尾巴上的大钉子就是那些药物的副产品?
- We believe the serum is responsible. - Well done, doctor.
- 我们相信是血清引起的. - 干得不错,博士.
Do you think I intended this? We were developing a drug...
你认为我是故意得?我们在制造一种...
- that would save lives. - I think you failed there.
- 可以拯救生命的药物 - 我想你们失败了.
No, no. We didn't fail. We were on the cusp of a breakthrough.
不,不,我们没有失败 我们即将取得重大突破
But there's a reason why I came along.
但我来这里还有原因
I don't like where this is going.
我不喜欢这样
I don't know how it could get any worse.
我想情况不会比这更糟了
She's pregnant.
她怀孕了
I was wrong.
我错了
- The female is about to give birth. - When?
- 母蛇就要产卵了. - 何时?
In less than 24 hours, if not sooner.
24小时内,可能更快
Normal little snakes, right?
普通的小蛇,时吗?
Like the black one.
想黑色的那条
Why the hell would you allow something like that?
你他妈的怎么能让这样的事情发生?
For research. The offspring would put us closer to perfecting the serum.
为了研究,那些后代可以让免疫血清更完美
Serum. And just what was this serum supposed to do besides wreak havoc?
血清,除了破坏这些血清还有什么用?
A giant step towards the cure for cancer and Alzheimer's disease.
为功课癌症和老年痴呆 迈进一大步
Giant's the operative word here.
一大步是个很关键的词哦
We can sit and argue about this or we can do something.
我们是坐下来争论 还是采取措施补救
In less than 24 hours this country's gonna be overrun.
24小时内这个国家就要遭殃了
- Give me the SAT phone. - What?
- 给我卫星电话. - 什么?
- Calling the military. - Good call.
- 打电话给军队. - 好主意
- You wanna do that? - What else is there?
- 你想这么做? - 我们还能做什么?
- Hold on. Let's hear Hammett out. - Our mission is based on secrecy.
- 等等让Hammett把话说完 - 我们的任务是秘密的.
Call the military, we're kissing our paychecks goodbye.
叫来军队, 我们可就要吻别支票了.
There are thousands... No, millions of lives at stake here.
有上千... 不,上百万人命处在危险中
- Make that call. - Wanna go to jail?
- 打电话. - 想进监狱吗?
- I heard transgenics were illegal. - Better 10-by-10 than 6 feet under.
- 我听说转基因是违法的 - 坐牢总比杀人好.
She's right. We're not equipped to deal with this, no way to find them.
她是对的,我们没有受过这种训练,没有办法找到他们
I disagree. Our chances are excellent. I know where the snakes are.
我不同意,我们有很好的机会 我知道蛇在哪里
- How? - I shot one with a tracker.
- 你怎么知道? - 我射了一个追踪器在他们中的一条身上.
One that can't be shed.
是不会随蜕皮掉落的那种
Besides...
另外...
...wanna call in the military?
...还想叫军队吗?
They won't be here in time.
他们不可能及时到达
You better be right.
你最好是对的
- Coffee? - Sure. Thanks.
- 咖啡? - 好的,谢谢.
Look...
看...
...maybe we got off on the wrong foot.
...也许我们有点出师不利
Oh, I see. You've come here to apologize, have you?
哦,我知道了.你来这里忏悔的,是吗?
No. Actually, I came here to offer you a job.
不,事实是我来给你一份工作做
Well, then, I'd have to question your intelligence.
哦,那我就不得不怀疑你的智商了
Why is that?
为什么?
Because you're the great white hunter and I'm with the Ph.D., remember?
因为你是伟大的白人猎人,我是博士,还记得吗?
I just hope that you're as good as everybody says you are.
我只是希望你跟大家所说的一样优秀
No. I'm better.
不,我比他们说的还要棒
Got it.
找到了
- The old industrial park. - Okay, let's go.
- 老工业园区 - 好,我们走
- You don't have to go. - One of us needs to stay.
- 你不比去. - 我们中间有一个需要留下.
- You good with that? - Sure.
- 你没问题把? - 当然.
Be our eyes. If anything changes, let us know immediately.
帮我们盯着,要是有情况第一时间告诉我们
Got it.
明白
Straight ahead.
往前走
- Pinkus? - Yeah.
- Pinkus? - 嗯.
Stay back and cover us, huh?
呆后面掩护我们,好吗?
Okay.
好的
You're almost right on top of it.
你们很接近它了
It's got to be in here.
它就在里面
Now.
现在
I go high.
我负责上面
- Low left. - Low right.
- 左下. - 右下
One, two, three.
1,2,3
Oh, no.
哦,不
Sofia.
Pinkus.
Pinkus, hold on.
Pinkus, 坚持住.
They're coming this way. I need backup.
他们向这边来了,我需要支援
Amanda's spotted the snakes. We'll be right there.
Amanda看到蛇了 我们就来
Leave him. There's nothing we can do. Leave him.
放弃他,我们无能为力,放弃吧
Sorry.
对不起
I saw them go this way.
我看见他们朝这边走了
Let me guess. They swim.
让我猜猜,他们会游泳.
Unfortunately, very well.
不幸,技术还很牛
This is where they went in.
这里是他们跑掉的地方
- What's the temperature of that water? - Forty, maybe 50 degrees.
- 水温多少? - 40,或者50.
Well, they're cold-blooded, so they can only last, like, 20 or 30 minutes.
很好,他们是冷血动物,所以他们最多只能维持 20-30分钟
Thirty minutes. Seven miles an hour.
30分钟,7英里每小时.
Puts them on that side of the lake.
够他们游到湖的另一边
They would swim until they found a food source.
他们会一直游 直到找到食物
Which means...
这个意味着...
What?
什么?
- She's about to give birth. - What are you saying?
- 她马上就要生了. - 你在说什么?
The anaconda lays their young next to an abundant food supply.
蟒蛇会把卵产在有充足食物的地方
The city.
那座城市
- What can we do? - Find out where they went.
- 我们该怎么做? - 把他们找出来
- And we keep tracking. - Keep tracking? Are you nuts?
- 我们继续追踪. - 继续?你疯了吗?
Half our crew is dead. If we had called this in like Amanda...
我们小队咯屁一半了 加入我们听Amanda叫军队的话...
Nobody wanted this, man.
没有人想这样的,兄弟
Let me tell you a bit about the military.
让我跟你说是军队把
They're as reliable as a bottle of Jack at an AA meeting.
他们跟戒酒协会的见面会上的啤酒一样不可靠
You are full of it. You've done nothing but get us killed.
是你不可靠 你除了让我们咯屁还能做什么?
Let me paint you a clearer picture.
让我给你描述一下
In about 12 hours, this entire country is gonna be overrun...
12小时后,整个国家都要遭殃了...
...with baby snakes that will eat you and everything in their paths.
...小蛇会把你和敢挡他们道的任何东西吃光光
Now, we can either find them and stop them or we can call in the military.
现在,我们可以找到并且阻止他们, 或者打电话叫军队来
- Call them. - Andrei, give me the SAT phone.
- 叫军队 - Andrei, 给我卫星电话
Yeah, it's Hammett.
喂, 我是Hammett.
Put me through to Major Reysner.
帮我接一下Reysner少校.
Major, a situation has arisen that requires your urgent assistance.
少校,有个紧急情况,需要你的支援
A 100-foot mutated anaconda...
一条长100尺的变种巨蟒...
...has escaped a confined facility near Baiton.
...从Baiton附近的禁区逃跑了.
We've been tracking it for two days. We lost five men.
我们追踪了2天,被干掉了5个人
Now our concern is for the local citizens.
现在我们当心会波及当地居民
We need backup ASAP.
我们要马上支援.
Thank you. I'll alert my team.
谢谢,我会通知我的队伍
I'll keep the SAT phone on and triangulate our position.
我会开着卫星电话来确定我们的方位
Andrei, keep it on.
Andrei, 让电话一直开着
Everyone happy?
都满意了吗?
Now, you got two choices.
现在,你有两个选择
You go home with a great snake story or you go with me.
带着巨蟒故事回家 或者跟我来
I intend on getting a nice new pair...
我打算明天做一双...
...of anaconda snakeskin boots in the morning.
...漂亮的蟒皮新靴子来穿穿.
Five more minutes, honey.
还有五分钟,宝贝.
Your father will be home soon.
你老爸就要回到家了
I got you.
我找到你了.
- What do you see? - Unnatural patterns in the bushes.
- 你看到了什么? - 灌木丛有点反常.
Patterns in the dirt.
泥土里有图案.
Every animal's got his stamp. You just gotta know how to find them.
所有队伍都有他们自己的脚印 只要你知道怎么找
Call the others.
通知其他人
Hammett's found the trail. We're heading northwest.
Hammett找到踪迹了,我们正朝西北前进
Our coordinates are 64982 by 450938. Over.
我们坐标是64982 450938.完毕.
We're heading west now.
我们正朝西走
We should intersect Fairago Road...
我们在菲尔雷葛路会合...
...about 2.1 kilometers from your location.
...大约离你们2.1公里
Assuming that you stay on that heading.
按照你们前进的方向.
Sounds right. Out.
好的,完毕
Okay. Turn here.
好的,这里转弯
What?
怎么了?
We're less than a quarter mile from our rendezvous?
离我们会合点不到1/4英里了?
- Right. - We have 20 minutes till they get here.
- 对. - 他们到这里还要20分钟.
What are you getting at?
什么意思?
That factory is everything a giant snake would want in a home.
那个工厂正是巨蟒要产卵的地方.
We have weapons and the time. Let's go.
我们有武器和时间,我们上
Yeah, I'm with you.
好,一起去
What is it?
怎么了?
Trail just disappeared.
踪迹消失了
- It can't just disappear. - Yeah, I know.
- 不可能突然消失的. - 是是,我知道
It's gotta be here somewhere.
它一定就在附近
The trees.
树上.
Look out!
小心!
- You okay? - Yeah.
- 你没事吧? - 还好.
But I think God wants us to fail.
但我想老天想要我们失败
Not just yet, pal. Not just yet.
还不是,伙计,还不是.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
哦 你不是在开玩笑吧
Well, at least we've established a rendezvous.
至少我们已经确定了会合的地点
Let's get the hell out of here.
让我们离开这个鬼地方
Take a look at this.
你瞧瞧这个
Well, if there's blood, there's more blood.
哇,假如这是血,那将有更多的血
Let's find it.
让我们找找看.
Bingo.
找到了
This snake just made our job a hell of a lot easier.
这条蛇让我们追踪起来他妈的简单多了
Let's go.
我们走
- Did you see that? - Yeah.
- 你看见了吗? - 是的
We got a visual on the snake, 20 degrees west of your location.
我们看到蛇了 在你西边20度.
- Old abandoned power plant. - Try him again.
- 旧废弃电厂. - 再呼叫一次.
Andrei, do you copy?
Andrei, 听到请回答?
- I guess we're on our own. - Give me the biggest gun you have.
- 我猜只能靠自己了 - 把最大的枪拿来.
- How cute. - Just kidding.
- 真精致. - 开玩笑.
This big enough for you. It will have to do for now.
这把够大了吧,关键时刻就靠它了
We're clear.
安全
You ready for this?
准备好了吗你?
Not even remotely.
还差得远呢
Attagirl.
好女孩
Nice apartment.
好公寓
We saw it come in here, right?
我们看到它进来了,是吗?
It would've been hard to miss.
它跑不了了
This must be the guestroom.
这里一定是会客厅
Yeah.
嗯
I say we go over there.
我们到那边去
Okay.
好
- The blood, here's the snake's blood. - Yeah.
- 血,这里有蛇血. - 对
That makes me feel a lot better.
这让我感觉好多了
There's more right here.
那里更多
Hold on. Hold on.
等等,等等
Clear.
安全
You got my back?
你掩护我?
I got your back.
我掩护你
- They're playing hide and seek? - Watch out!
- 他们在玩捉迷藏? - 小心!
It's just rats.
那只是老鼠.
It's only rats.
那只是老鼠
Just snake snacks.
只是蛇得点心
Hammett.
That's it. All right, keep up.
那里,对了,跟上.
Where'd he go?
它哪里去了?
No!
不!
Wait! Stop!
等等,停下!
No!
不!
Shoot me.
向我开枪.
Damn it, Amanda! Take me out!
该死的, Amanda! 把我弄出去!
What are you doing?
你在做什么?
Nick, no!
Nick,不要!
What are you doing? No!
你在做什么? 不要!
No! Don't do it!
不! 别这么做!
What do I do?
我到底做了什么?
Run!
快跑!
Hurry!
快!
- Give me the SAT phone. - We have to help them.
- 把卫星电话给我. - 我们得救他们.
You go on ahead. I'm gonna check back.
你先走,我要打电话检查一下.
Four miles northeast of location.
东北4英里的方位
The old power plant.
旧废弃电厂
You can't miss it.
你不会错过它的 .
Murdoch residence.
Murdoch寓所.
It's Mr. Reysner. Please, put me through to Murdoch.
我是Reysner先生. 请帮我接通Murdoch先生.
Just a second, sir.
稍等,先生
Mr. Murdoch, Mr. Reysner on line for you.
Murdoch先生, Reysner先生有电话找你
Tell him, I'll call him back on the other line.
告诉它,我用另一条线回给他
Yes, sir.
是,先生
I told you not to call me on any line but this one.
我告诉过你除了这条线其他都可以打.
Sorry. It won't happen again.
抱歉,不会再发生了.
I wanted to let you know that everything is going as planned.
我想让你知道一切都照计划进行
We're right on schedule.
一切尽在掌握
Good.
很好
No one must know anything about this.
不要让其他人知道
That won't be a problem.
没问题
Just make sure our money's in place.
只管准备好付给我们的钱就可以了.
Oh, God.
哦,老天
Oh, my God, I thought you guys were dead.
哦,我的上帝 我以为你们已经死了
- Our radio was broken. - Where's Nick?
- 我们的无线电坏了 - Nick哪儿去了?
- He's dead and so is the black one. - The queen?
- 他和黑蛇同归于尽了. - 蟒后呢?
- I think it's down that hall. - What's this?
- 我想它从走廊下去了. - 这是什么?
- It's a slug. - A what?
- 蛇卵的壳 - 什么?
- An infertile membrane, a dead egg. - What?
- 一张枯萎的外膜,一粒已死的蛇卵. - 什么?
- She's about to start laying. - Then let's finish this and get out!
- 她要开始产卵了. - 那就让我们做个了结然后离开
Sixty seconds will give us enough time.
60秒,留给我们的时间足够
We'll blow this whole place.
我们把这里一锅端了
What the hell? Hammett?
他妈的怎么回事? Hammett?
Quite a sight, isn't it?
很壮观,不是吗?
The miracle of birth.
奇迹的诞生日
I can't believe you wanna destroy something so beautiful.
我不能相信你要毁掉如此美丽的东西
Toss the gun down, soldier girl.
放下枪,女兵
What?
怎么?
You don't think I'd shoot you?
你认为我不会开枪吗?
Good girl.
真棒
You have no idea what you're doing.
你根本就不知道自己在做什么
I think I do.
我想我知道
Ten million dollars for just one baby snake.
一千万美金一条幼蛇
You're working with Murdoch?
你在给Murdoch干活?
You are not a doctor for nothing.
你还不笨
There's no special forces unit, is there?
也不会有特种兵来,是吗?
Two for two.
说对了
Why don't you just shoot me?
你为什么不开枪?
Well, you could be a meal.
哦,你可以给蛇做点心.
Or you could take a bullet and be a meal.
或者带颗子弹做点心
Or you could work for a brand-new employer...
右或者为全新的老板工作...
...who could use your expertise in continuing the research.
...谁可以利用你的专业技术来继续开展研究
You cut me in on the 10 million?
一千万美金有我的一份吗?
Negotiable.
可以考虑
Okay.
好
Not!
做梦!
So you wanna play.
那么你是想玩玩了
I'm trying to be nice to you.
我试着对你温柔点
Happy trails, slimy bitch.
狗日的,臭婊子
Your 10 mil's about to go up in flames, Hammett.
你的一千万就要变成灰烬了 Hammett.
I hope that's not the only thing.
我希望你也一样
Good knowing you.
很高兴认识你
Reysner, you have a package for me?
Reysner,你有包裹要给我吗
Yes, Mr. Murdoch, I have one. I will begin research immediately.
是的Murdoch先生, 有一个.我会立刻着手研究
You show me proof...
给我看看证据...
...the money will be wired direct to your account.
...我就把钱直接汇到你帐号.